<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Site on Brewing Cats</title>
    <link>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Site on Brewing Cats</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 20:35:07 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Link Tree</title>
      <link>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/linktree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 17:20:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/linktree/</guid>
      <description>Promoted Content  OpenSea Profile   Brewing Cats on OpenSea  read more      NFT Projects   Learn about our NFT projects  read more      Mexican Lottery on NFT First Edition   Welcome to the First Edition of Mexican Lottery Board Game NFT!  read more      Ola Interpreting   Partner Site for Ola Interpreting LLC, certified interpreters  read more      HugoBelin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telemetry</title>
      <link>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/telemetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 21:38:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/telemetry/</guid>
      <description>In order to measure our criteria of success with our website (that is to provide a delightful experience to our users) we need to know and understand how it is being used. We plan to achieve this through the use of telemetry data, this data will provide us insights regarding any usability issues, what type of content users enjoy the most, and other types of issues
The use of telemetry is a common and accepted practice for most websites, nowadays users aren&amp;rsquo;t even informed about this, let alone letting them know about the usage given to this data (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 16:30:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/about/</guid>
      <description>Brewing Cats  Brewing Delightful Software
 Brewing Cats LLC is a small, independent company looking to enrich the web with quality content in several areas. Its owners do it in a fun and respectful way. Key focus areas are entertainment (movies, video games, and more) as well as software development. We have a special view of how the web should work and we try to lead by example</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Policy</title>
      <link>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 17:34:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/policy/</guid>
      <description>Terms of Use Do the good and not the evil. Use of this website imply that you agree with the terms of use stated below. That being said Brewing Cats operates with certain amounts of data which are used in different ways to improve the functionality of the website as well as to enable interoperability with other sites on the web. The data being generated due to its use will be used in a fair and transparent way, we believe that the data generated by a single user can help us make a better website by improving, optimizing, and allowing us to know the key investments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2020 21:53:43 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>This website is created over a common core which is used for other websites. It packs specific features and functionality that make Brewing Cats a better site. Brewing Cats Core augments the base functionality from our main repo based on Hugo using Ananke Theme This post showcases the completed work as well as the upcoming features. These can be tracked in the following AirTable board:
    $(&#39;article&#39;).css(&#39;max-width&#39;, &#39;100%&#39;);    BrewingCatsCore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 19:46:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/credits/</guid>
      <description>This post was created to recognize the hard work of the many developers that made this site possible thus far. From hosting, to frameworks, they&amp;rsquo;re recognized here:
Hosting, Libraries, Frameworks and other Technologies   BrewingCatsCore.Logger.traceInfo( `AirTable Component`, &#39;component.airtable&#39;, &#39;tagId_10&#39;, &#39;ComponentSetup&#39;, { &#39;component&#39;: &#39;AirTable&#39;, &#39;tableId&#39;: &#39;shraGTO9M4qs0Th5v&#39; } );  Media   Unsplash: Beer Collection - Main Page image by @rawpixel    Image Credits: Unsplash: Mac Keyboard image by @fantasyflip    Site Views: 0  Page Views: 0  Your Site Views: 0  Your Page Views: 0   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 12:17:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brewingcats.com/posts/site/changelog/</guid>
      <description>Changes made to the website are recorded in this post for tracking purposes
Version: 3.27.27 Release: Han Solo  Versioning Policies Major.Minor.Build  | | |_______ Brewing Cats Core Version  | |_____________ New features  |___________________ Official new releases (Tied to a Release name)
 Milestone Naming Conventions Milestone names are taken from:
  List of Star Wars characters then:  Star Wars Legends characters then:  Star Wars Rebels characters then:  Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic characters then:  Star Wars cast members then:  Star Wars: The Clone Wars cast members   Release milestone would look like:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
